A 9 -year -old Central California boy braved strong currents and cold water to swim
from San Francisco to Alcatraz Island and back.
A California television station in Fresno reported Tuesday that James Savage set a
record as the youngest swimmer to make the journey to the former prison.
as the youngest swimmer to make the journey to the former prison.
The TV station reported that by completing the swim, the fourth grade student from
Los Baños broke a record previously held by a 10 -year -old boy.
Los broke a record previously held by a 10 -year -old boy.
The TV station reported that by completing the swim, fourth grade student from Los
Baños broke a record previously held by a 10 -year -old boy.
James said that waves in the San Francisco Bay hitting him in the face 30 minutes
into his swim made him want to give up.
James said said that waves in the San Francisco Bay hitting him in the face 30
minutes into his swim made him want to give up.
said that waves in the San Francisco Bay hitting him in the face 30 minutes into his
swim made him want to give up.
His father said he had offered his son $100 as a reward.
To encourage his struggling son,
he doubled it to $200.
His father said he had offered his son $100 as a reward.
To encourage his struggling son,
he doubled